## JACKSON BOULTER

#### **SKILLS**

- Time Management Skills
- · Business Analysis
- Software Development

- Customer Service Experience
- Network Administration
- DevOps Practices

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Valuable team contributor with strong organizational capabilities and being effective at prioritizing tasks and meeting deadlines. Alongside academic, professional and personal experience in general programming practices and the vast world of network administration. Please refer to my personal website located on the header for a look into my various projects!

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### EDI/IT CONSULTANT 03/2024 to Current

CONTAX Inc., Charlottetown, PE

- Manage EDI communication between various companies.
- Ability to work independently and troubleshoot various software systems.
- Proficiency in Microsoft 365 software products (Excel, Word, etc), and knowledge of SAP's suite of products.
- Create and maintain up to date documentation.
- Communicate with clients, gather requirements for projects, and the ability to accurately implement/act on the requests in a timely manner.

#### **LAB ASSISTANT** 09/2023 to 12/2023

University of Prince Edward Island, Charlottetown, PE

- Assist first and second year students in completing lab work
- Have deep understanding of learning material and ability to express it in simple terms

#### **HOUSEKEEPING STAFF** 06/2023 to 09/2023

Green Gables Bungalow Court and Cottages, Cavendish, PE

- Participate in morning briefings to understand the various tasks for the day
- Majority of work is done independently (or in small teams), responsible for all aspects of cleaning rental cottages (taking out trash, disinfecting common areas, sweeping/mopping)
- Collaborated with maintenance staff to address any repair needs or safety concerns in a timely manner.

#### **LABORER** 05/2020 to 09/2022

Captain Cookes, Borden-Carleton, PE

• Trained to handle various parts of the production process, general labor

- Involved in loading shipping containers while adhering to strict time schedules
- Maintaining a clean work station

# **CASHIER & PREP COOK** 04/2019 to 09/2019 **C&T Convenience/BlueGoose**, DeSable, PE

- Front of house duties, including cash and cleaning
- Prepare various ingredients for tomorrow's crew
- Performed cash, and card transactions to complete customer purchases.

#### **EDUCATION**

**UPEI**, Charlottetown, PE

Bachelor of Science, Major in Computer Science, 12/2023

**Bluefield High School**, North Wiltshire, PE **High School Diploma**, 12/2018

#### **REFERENCES**

**Upon Request**